<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>IKY.LI - It&#39;s Ivan</title>
    <link>https://iky.li/</link>
    <description>Recent content on IKY.LI - It&#39;s Ivan</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <managingEditor>ivan@iky.li (Ivan Li)</managingEditor>
    <webMaster>ivan@iky.li (Ivan Li)</webMaster>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://iky.li/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Kick-ass Agile Team</title>
      <link>https://iky.li/posts/kick-ass-agile-teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>ivan@iky.li (Ivan Li)</author>
      <guid>https://iky.li/posts/kick-ass-agile-teams/</guid>
      <description>Team startup has been on the fore-front of my mind lately because we&amp;rsquo;re just about to go through a re-structure. Sitting over a coffee, I took some time to think about what sort of team I really want to be part of and create. It really wasn&amp;rsquo;t a difficult choice: a world-class team that could tackle any challenges thrown their way.
A team like this would be a well-oiled learning and discovery machine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Taking Extreme Ownership</title>
      <link>https://iky.li/posts/taking-extreme-ownership/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>ivan@iky.li (Ivan Li)</author>
      <guid>https://iky.li/posts/taking-extreme-ownership/</guid>
      <description>This post is a WIP.
 I don&amp;rsquo;t claim to have a whole deal of experience with this concept, it&amp;rsquo;s a new area I&amp;rsquo;m exploring with other colleagues at work. Certainly it&amp;rsquo;s been game changing even just reflecting on how I&amp;rsquo;m approaching ownership, where it begins and where it ends.
The concept of extreme ownership comes from the book written by Jocko Willink &amp;mdash; former US Navy SEAL leader.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leadership Grind Lightning Talks</title>
      <link>https://iky.li/posts/leadership-grind-lightning-talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>ivan@iky.li (Ivan Li)</author>
      <guid>https://iky.li/posts/leadership-grind-lightning-talks/</guid>
      <description>The Leadership Grind meetup held a lightning talk night on 15 August 2018. A few of us from the team went along and took away some learnings and insights.
Here&amp;rsquo;s what stood out for me on the night.
Recognition and Feedback It&amp;rsquo;s great to see Xero performing internal research on it&amp;rsquo;s own ability to give recognition to employees. Not many companies travel down this road of retrospection and are comfortable with sharing the results and learnings.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Productivity with Kanban For One</title>
      <link>https://iky.li/posts/kanban-for-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>ivan@iky.li (Ivan Li)</author>
      <guid>https://iky.li/posts/kanban-for-one/</guid>
      <description>KanbanFor1 is a personal time management tool I&amp;rsquo;ve been using for a while now. I thought I&amp;rsquo;d share the learnings I&amp;rsquo;ve gained into the way that works best for me.
It&amp;rsquo;s good at getting me focussed No matter what technique you use, managing your focus is an activity that requires a lot of discipline. For me, being able to stay focussed on one task gave me the biggest boost in productivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Experience With Impact Mapping</title>
      <link>https://iky.li/posts/experience-with-impact-mapping/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>ivan@iky.li (Ivan Li)</author>
      <guid>https://iky.li/posts/experience-with-impact-mapping/</guid>
      <description>In recent times, I got the opportunity to apply the Impact Mapping technique designed by Gojko Adzic to the area of DevOps within our embedded software team. I knew about the technique a while back when Gojko made his appearance in Auckland as part of the Agile Auckland meetup almost 3 years ago.
I was looking for a way to express the vision and purpose of the team, while creating a strong and obvious link to the stories we will be doing everyday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Read my README</title>
      <link>https://iky.li/posts/read-my-readme/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <author>ivan@iky.li (Ivan Li)</author>
      <guid>https://iky.li/posts/read-my-readme/</guid>
      <description>This README is a documentation of me. You can get a good gist of what I do and what I&amp;rsquo;m here to achieve in the F&amp;amp;P CPAP software team.
Important: NOT a replacement for actually getting to know each other more.
My Job I&amp;rsquo;m the outcome owner for DevOps sub-team in the CPAP software team. This means I&amp;rsquo;m ultimately accountable for the development and release processes adopted for the 3 sub-teams.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>